ispg.in 2014-03-01

# ISPG Web Design Web & Mobile App Development Company Privacy Policy

[www.ispg.in](http://www.ispg.in/) (hence by referred to as "ISPG or "we", or "us ) is owned by ISPG Technologies India Pvt. Ltd. ISPG provides this Privacy Policy to inform Users of ISPG's [www.ispg.in](http://www.ispg.in/) Web Site (hereinafter referred to as "Web Site') of ISPG's policies and procedures regarding the collection, use and disclosure of personally identifiable information received from Users of the Web Site. If you elect to submit any personal information, your submission is subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy and you consent to such terms.

By using the Web Site and/or services offered/advertised through it and/or ISPG, you are consenting to ISPG's processing of User's information as set forth in this Privacy Policy now and as amended by ISPG from time to time. Keep in mind that use of ISPG's services is also subject to, and controlled by, the Agreement subscribed to by the User; and use of the Web Site is subject to the Terms and Conditions notified on the Web Site.

ISPG respect your privacy and are committed to protecting personal information that you may share with us. This Privacy Policy describes how we may collect and use your personal information.

####  Information We Collect

Personal information means any information that may be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to, a first and last name, email address, a home, postal or other physical address, other contact information, title, occupation, industry, personal interests, and other information when needed to provide a service or product or carry out a transaction you have requested. 

####  Notice

When personal information is collected, ISPG will inform you at the point of collection the purpose for the collection. ISPG will not transfer your personal information to third parties without your consent, except under the limited conditions described under the section entitled "Information Sharing and Disclosure" below. 

####  Information Sharing and Disclosure

####  ISPG do not transfer or share your information except as provided below:

**1\. ISPG may also send your personal information to other companies or people if:**

ISPG have users' consent to share the information; 

ISPG may share User's personally identifiable information with our resellers and partners, so that such resellers and partners may use such information to market ISPG's products and services, and to market their own products and services. ISPG may engage certain trusted third parties to perform function and provide services to us, including without limitation, hosting and management services, customer relationship services, database storage and management services, fulfilling orders, sending email, processing credit card payments or other functions necessary to our business; and ISPG may share your personally identifiable information with these third parties, but only to the extent necessary to perform these functions and provide such services, and only pursuant to binding contractual obligations requiring such third parties to maintain confidentiality of your data. 

ISPG may also reveal a user's identity or relevant information if ISPG knows or believes that User is harming or interfering with other our users, anyone else, or violating the Agreement or infringing any of the ISPG's legal rights. 

ISPG may also reveal user's personal information when required to do so by law, or if we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a court order or subpoena, to cooperate with investigations by law enforcement or regulatory authorities or to participate or cooperate with a judicial proceeding, or in urgent circumstances, to protect personal safety, the public or our websites; to protect the property and rights of ISPG or a third party, the safety of the public or any person; to prevent or stop any illegal, unethical or legally actionable activity.

In the event of a merger, consolidation or reorganization involving ISPG, acquisition of ISPG by another company, or other similar transaction, your personal information will, in most instances, be transferred to the control of the third party that is part of that transaction. 

####  **Data Security**

ISPG employs reasonable and current security methods to prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure correct use of information. No data transmission over the internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be secure and therefore ISPG cannot ensure or guarantee the security of any information User transmits to ISPG and User does so at his/her own risk. 

**Kindly note:**

ISPG is not responsible for the privacy practices of other web sites linked from ISPG's Web Site. Users are required to read the privacy policies or statements of other such web sites they visit. 

ISPG is not directed to persons under age of 18 years and does not knowingly collect, either online or offline, information from such individuals. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided ISPG with personally identifiable information without their consent, he or she should contact us at ISPG. If ISPG becomes aware that a child under the age of 18 years has provided ISPG with personally identifiable information, ISPG will remove such information from their files. 

Any legal action or proceedings relating to or arising out of this Privacy Policy shall be settled in the courts and/or tribunals in Ernakulum in the State of Kerala, India. 

ISPG may change this Privacy Policy from time to time by posting updated policies on the Web Site.
